firmpay.com 2004-06-03

# FirmPay.Com - Software that makes the wheels of eCommerce Turn!

**Privacy Policy**

PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING CAREFULLY.  
THE AFOREMENTIONED IS THE PRIVACY POLICY THAT GOVERNS YOUR USE OF ANY FirmPay SERVICES.  

This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") applies to FirmPay  

As revised on: November 10, 2003  

At FirmPay, we recognize the privacy needs of our Customers. You should be able to choose what information you want to share and decide what will happen to that information once it has been shared. Protecting your personal information is vitally important. Please read the following Privacy Policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our many offerings. This policy may change from time to time without notice so please check back periodically. We hope this will increase your awareness about online privacy. 

**Collected Information**  
If you choose to use and or purchase a FirmPay product or place an order with us, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, physical and electronic mail ("e-mail") addresses, phone number, domain name and other information that by itself, or in combination with other information, may be identifiable to you as a specific individual. We may also ask for financial information, such as account or credit card numbers, and demographic information, such as your zip code. 

Please be aware that FirmPay advertisers, and web sites that have links on our sites, and provider/distributor partners may also collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of these Internet access partners, advertisers, and web sites linked to FirmPay and provider/distributor partners, are not governed by this Privacy Policy. What these other sites do with that information is governed by the privacy policy for that site and not this policy. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy on any site you visit. 

**Information Requests**  
You may be able to request information on our sites regarding products and Services, including technical support and customer Service, by using online forms. We may ask that you provide certain contact information to allow us to fulfill your request and to send you information about FirmPay products and Services. 

**Security**  
Ordering online for a FirmPay product or service is secure and convenient. Our ordering process is protected by the Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") protocol, which encrypts your information and confirms the identity of the FirmPay server before completing your transaction. Netscape Navigator 2.0 + (or better) and Internet Explorer 3.0+ (or better) support the SSL protocol. We recommend you use the latest browsers to ensure that you are protected by advances in security technology. 

**Disclosure**  
FirmPay will not sell, rent, trade, or disclose individual Customer information to any third parties or outside companies who will use the information to contact you or who will share the information with others without your permission. It may be necessary to disclose information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating FirmPay policies or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of FirmPay, other FirmPay users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. FirmPay may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and Services. 

**Use of Information**  
The use of an individual's e-mail address is necessary to keep our Customers well informed of maintenance issues, escalated critical issues and problem resolutions that may arise with your FirmPay Service. We may also use e-mail addresses to provide our Customers with informative newsletters. 

We like to keep our Customers informed via e-mail and other means. Sometimes Stringer Software Solutions uses personal and demographic information to help us determine which FirmPay products and Services are most likely to be of interest to you or help diagnose problems with our servers or administration of our sites. We also use demographic information to gather general interest in our products, to help in the analysis of product usage, purchasing, and target markets. 

Please note that FirmPay does provide information to outside companies (such as a credit card processing company) who perform certain functions on our behalf for billing purposes. We will not permit those companies to use the gathered information for other than the stated purpose. 

**Correct/Update**  
If you want to change or modify information you have previously provided to us, please contact us by sending an e-mail to: support@firmpay.com 

**Cookies**  
Some of the websites we host place small bits of text or "cookies" onto your computer's hard drive. Cookies enable us to deliver content specific to your interests and keep track of your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our web sites. After you accept a cookie, it is passed from your browser to our servers each time you request a page. This cookie consists of a unique token that anonymously identifies to the server so that you can more easily access the features of the FirmPay Service. Please note that you may configure your web browser to warn you before you accept a cookie. 

**Customer E-mails**  
FirmPay will not read or disclose e-mail content to others unless required by law or deemed necessary to operate our services. 

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about FirmPay privacy policy or the privacy practices of our web sites, please contact us by sending an e-mail to support@firmpay.com 

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**  
In the event our Privacy Policy needs to be modified, those changes will be reflected in the next revision of this Privacy Policy which will be posted on the FirmPay web site. Please check back often to review any revisions.
